https://www.conns.com/privacy-policy

Home
Credit Privacy Policy
Credit Privacy Policy
To View the Credit Privacy Policy, click here.
Credit Privacy Policy - English (Printable)
Credit Privacy Policy - Spanish (Printable)
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-877-358-1252 or send us an email at customerservice@conns.com.
Third party and Social Media Information Sharing
We also may work with third-party service providers, including Facebook, to show you specific advertisements and promotions on your devices that we think you may be interested in, via both online and offline channels (including social media), as well as to ensure our marketing efforts are effective. Third-party service providers, as well as Conn’s HomePlus, may collect personally identifiable information through cookies, web beacons and other storage technologies about your online behavior throughout time, as well as across multiple websites and services.
How You Can Opt Out
You have every right to opt out of the above summarized information sharing. If you wish to opt out of information gathering described above, you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. In addition, we encourage you to review Facebook’s Data Policy at https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy.
